Guide to the Burton Hall Papers WAG.087
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: 2007-2008 accretion
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974' Funds v. Nastasi White: Case # 91-CIV-0650, 1990 (Box 34)
  - Alfarone v. Standard Drywall: Case # CV-81-015, 1980s (Box 34)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: Case # 81-CIV-0337, 1987-1990 (Box 34)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: Case # 81-CIV-0337, 1982-1989 (Box 35)
  - Drywall Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White: Case # 91-CIV-0650, 1990 (Box 36)
  - US v. Mason Tenders District Council, 1994 (Box 36)
  - State of NY v. John F. O'Connor, 1987 (Box 36)
  - Trustees of the Tapers Local 1974 Funds v. Bernie Wolff Construction et al, etc. 91-CIV-0634, etc., 1991 (Box 36)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (Case # 81-CIV-0337), 1985 (Box 36)
  - Drywall Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White (Case # 91-CIV-0650), 1991 (Box 36)
  - People v. Bitondo and Hanley, 1990 (Box 36)
  - People v. O'Hara, undated (Box 36)
  - US v. Anthony "Fat Tony" Salerno, Vincent Dinapoli, "Fish" Cafaro, et al., Circa 1986 (Box 36)
  - Drywall Tapers' Funds case, 1995 (Box 36)
  - Petramale v. Local 17 and LIUNA, 1983; 1987 (Box 37)
  - Turner v. Air Transport Lodge of IAM and IAM, etc., Circa 1978 (Box 37)
  - BTEA (Building Trades Employers' Association) Arbitration Transcript, 1991 (Re: Plasterers' Local 60/Painters' D.C. 9) (Box 37)
  - Tapers Trustees v. Nastasi White, et. al., 1991 (Box 37)
  - Tapers v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s-early 1990s (Box 37)
  - Tapers and Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1970s (Box 37)
  - Putterman v. Knitwear, etc., 1973-1976 (Box 37)
  - Painters' DC9 Journal/Yearbook (1943) (Box 37)
  - Eatz v. NYRA, 91-9161 and 63, 1992 (Box 37)
  - Trustees v. Employer Trustees (Drywall Tapers), Circa 1985-1990 (Box 37)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1989-1992 (Box 37)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s-early 1990s (Box 38)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Jones v. Operative Plasterers, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Clay v. Castle Coal and Oil, 1994 (Box 38)
  - Rodonich v. Local 95 and LIUNA, 1986 (Box 38)
  - Drywall Tapers Trustees v. Bernie Wolff Construction et. al., 1980s (Box 38)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1979 (Box 38)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: 84-7137, 1980s (Box 39)
  - Alfarone, etc. and Drywall Tapers Fund Trustees v. Bernie Wolff Construction et. al., 1986 (Box 39)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1970s (Box 39)
  - Alfarone, et. al. V. Bernie Wolff et al., 1985 (Box 39)
  - Rodonich v. Housewreckers Union Local 95 and LIUNA, 1986,1994 (Box 40)
  - Alfarone v. Bernie Wolff, etc. et. al., 1973-1989 (Box 40)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s-1990s (Box 40)
  - Eric Frankland v. IAPE, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Plimack v. Nolan and NABET, 85 Civ. 4668 (Judge: LB Sand)(LMRDA case challenging retaliation against Plimack, a former NABET officer), Circa 1983-1985 (Box 41)
  - Lynn Bell (Bakery, etc. Workers' Union), Circa 1970s-1980s (Box 41)
  - Burton Hall's Bar Admission Certificates (1951, 1960s, 1985) (Box 41)
    Some certificates moved to Quarantine box 51A due to mold in July 2017.
  - Ralph Clay v. Castle Coal and Oil, Dept. Of Labor Case No. 90-STA-00037:(OSHA case by TDU member discharged for complaining about unsafe working conditions), Early 1990s (Box 42)
  - BTEA hearing transcripts, June 24, 1980, in Tapers and Plasterers jurisdictional dispute between Drywall Tapers Local 1974 & Plasterers Local 530 (Box 43)
  - The New York Plan for the Settlement of Jurisdictional Disputes, 1976 (Box 43)
  - Deposition transcripts: Tapers and Long v. Plasterers Int'l., 1976-1982 (Box 43)
  - Deposition Transcripts: De Rosa v. Blank (Drywall Tapers), 1977 (Box 43)
  - Deposition Transcripts: Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1982 (Box 43)
  - Deposition Transcripts: John Alfarone, et al. v. Standard Drywall Corp, et al., 1981-1982 (Box 43)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1982-1989 (Box 44)
  - US v. District Council of Carpenters (related organized crime prosecution), 1990 (Box 44)
  - State of NY v. Moscatiello, 1995 (Box 44)
  - John Alfarone et al. v. Nastasi-White, Inc., et al.: CV 84-3181, 1984 (Box 44)
  - Drywall Tapers Funds collections cases, Circa 1984-1985 (Box 44)
  - Plimack v. Nolan (85-CIV-4668), 1983-1985 (Box 44)
  - US v. District Council of Carpenters (90-CIV-5722), 1993 (Box 45)
  - Trustees of the Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, et al. (Component Assembly, Bernie Wolff...) (91-CIV- 0650, etc.), 1996 (Box 45)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CIV-0337), 1980s (Box 45)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1970s-1980s (Box 45)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council: Pertinent jurisdictional dispute documents, 1970s-1980s (Box 45)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CIV-0337), 1990 (Box 46)
  - Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White et al., 1980s (Box 46)
  - Putterman v. Knitgoods Workers Union, et al. (including ILGWU) (78 CIV 8000), Circa 1980s (Box 46)
  - Plimack v. Nolan and NABET, 85 Civ. 4668 (Judge: LB Sand), 1980s (Box 46)
  - Wall, et al. v. Construction and General Laborers Union, Local 230, et al., 1997-1998 (Box 46)
  - Pamphlet: Amalgamated Lithographers Local 1: By-laws, July 1974 (Box 46)
  - Pamphlet: Some Sample Provisions for Collective Bargaining Agreements: For the Guidance of Affiliates of the International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, AFL-CIO, 1970s (Box 47)
  - Pamphlet: NY State Department of Labor, 1960 (Box 47)
  - Trade Union Courier, June 1981 (Box 47)
  - Pamphlet: International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots Analysis of Labor-Management Relations Problems, June 1966 (Box 47)
  - Report: US House of Representatives Investigation of the Civil Rights Enforcement Activities of the Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs, US Dept. of Labor, May 1987 (Box 47)
  - Article: Bureau of National Affairs, "House Subcommittee Report on Labor Cites Growing Politicization of NLRB", 1984 (Box 47)
  - New Politics, Vol. IX, No. 3, January 1972 (Box 47)
  - Libertarian Analysis, Vol. 1 No. 4, December 1971 (Box 47)
  - National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 47)
  - National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 47)
  - US v. Bonanno Organized Crime Family of La Cost Nostra, et al, 1987 (Box 47)
  - US v. International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots International Maritime Division, 1972 (Box 47)
  - Confidential Memorandum Concerning Powell-Nazden Efforts to Clean up the Laborers' Union, August 1982 (Box 47)
  - Rosario, Vega and Cabel v. Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10 ILGWU, et al., 1984 (Box 47)
  - AFL-CIO Lawyers' Conference papers on public employees' rights, May 1982 (Box 47)
  - Earl Lucas v. Western Union International: NY City Commission on Human Rights, 1981-1989 (Box 47)
  - Drywall Tapers Contempt Litigation, June 1984 (Box 47)
  - Federal Labor Relations Authority Region II: Bureau of Labor Statistics, NY Region and National Council of Field Labor Locals, American Federation of Government Employees, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 47)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 (82-CIV-5583), 1983-1985 (Box 48)
  - Santos v. District Council, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Petramale v. LIUNA, 1983; 1987 (Box 49)
  - Union Trustees v. Employer Trustees (Drywall Tapers), 1983-1989 (Box 49)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s (Box 49)
  - Ted Kozera & RIchard M. Mekeel etc. et al. v. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, eta al, 1993 (Box 49)
  - Taper's Trustees v Nastasi-White et al (Bernie Wolff ... ) (91 Civ. 0650, etc.), 1981-1995 (Box 50)
  - Trustees of the Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, et al. (Component Assembly, Bernie Wolff), 1982; 1993-1996 (Box 51)
  - Eatz v. DME United of Local 3 & The New York Racing Association, 1960s; 1980s (Box 51A)
  - Tapers v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: 89-7127: petition for re-hearing, Circa 1989 (Box 51A)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: 91-7153: supplemental index, v. 3, 1980s-1990s (Box 51A)
  - Burton Hall's Bar Admission Certificates, 1951, 1960s, 1985 (Box 51A)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s; 1995 (Box 52)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Charles Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1975 (Box 52)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Charles Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1978 (Box 52)
  - Trustees of the Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, et al. (Component Assembly, Bernie Wolff), 1980s-1990s (Box 52)
  - John Alfarone v. Standard Drywall, 1982 (Box 53)
  - James Ricks v. American Radio Association, 1981 (Box 53)
  - John Alfarone v. Standard Drywall, 1984 (Box 53)
  - New York Times article: June 28, 1989, p. B4. "Grand Jury Vote Expected Soon in Union Inquiry," (Box 53)
  - US v. District Council of Carpenters, 1992 (Box 53)
  - Trustees of the Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, et al. (Component Assembly, Bernie Wolff), 1990s (Box 53)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s (Box 53)
  - Rodonich et al. v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA, 1980-1989 (Box 54)
  - Rodonich, Joseph, et al. v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA, 1981; 1986 (Box 55)
  - Rodonich-related: Raymond Donovan (US Secretary of Labor) and US Department of Labor and Rodonich, et al. v. House Wreckers' Union Local 95 of LIUNA, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Rodonich-related: NRLB charges re: Local 95 hiring hall practices, 1985 (Box 55)
  - John Hayes, Masters Mates & Pilots, 1986-1987 (Box 55)
  - Putterman v. Knitgoods Workers Union, et al. (including ILGWU) (78-Civ-6000, early 1980s (Box 55)
  - Petramale v. LIUNA (81-4817), 1980s (Box 55)
  - Drywall Tapers and Long, etc. v. Plasterers (75-CIV-4289) (Judge Metzner), Circa 1975-1979 (Box 57)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CIV-0337), 1980s (Box 57)
  - Alfarone et al v. Standard Drywall (81-CIV-0151). (Judge Bramwell), Early 1980s (Box 57)
  - Arbitration Between Union-Appointed Trustees of the Tapers Industry Insurance and Annuity Funds and Employer-Appointed Trustees of the Tapers Industry Insurance and Annuity Funds, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - Louis Caputo v. Solomon Salzhandler (US Supreme Court case no. 282), 1963 (Box 57)
  - Arbitration between Drywall Tapers and National Wall, Circa 1973 (Box 57)
  - Donovan v. Kaszycki 82 Civ 3287, 1982-1983 (Box 57)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CIV-0337), 1975-1984 (Box 57)
  - Alfarone, et al. v. Standard Drywall, et al. (81-CIV-0151), 1981 (Box 57)
  - Louis Caputo, President of NY DC 9 of Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, et al. v. Solomon Salzhandler, October 1963 (Box 57)
  - Max Sands, as Administrator of the Estate of Solomon Salzhandler v. Louis Caputo (President of DC 9, Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America), et al., 1967 (Box 58)
  - Samuel Winn v. Martin Rarback, 1961 (Box 58)
  - French v. Rarback, 1961 (Box 58)
  - Petramale v. LIUNA (81-4817), 1980s-1992 (Box 58)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1982 (Box 58)
  - Kozera et. al. V. Westchester-Fairfiled Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association, et. al., 1988 (Box 58)
  - Kozera et al. v. IBEW et. al., 1992-1994 (Box 58)
  - Putterman vs. ILGWU, Circa 1978 (Box 59)
  - Rodonich vs. Housewreckers and LIUNA, 1980s - 1990s (Box 59)
  - Kozera 1 (Kozera et al v. Westchester-Fairfield Chapter), 1989 (Box 59)
  - Kozera 2 ( (Kozera vs IBEW), 1995 (Box 59)
  - Petramale vs Local 17 and LIUNA, 1992 (Box 59)
  - Demolition Industry contractors and associates: criminal charges and complaints, 1988 (Box 59)
  - Newspaper clippings related to Rodonich case and LIUNA, 1970s-1980s (Box 59)
  - Wall and Cooksey v. Construction Laborer's Local 230, 1999 (Box 60)
  - Drywall Tapers: 2nd Circuit Appeal Briefs, 1984 (Box 60)
  - Drywall Tapers: Funds Case, 1989;1991 (Box 60)
  - Earl Lucas, et al. v. MCI Communications Corp, et al. (83 Civ. 2727), 1975-1988 (Box 60)
  - Related NLRB charges and decisions, undated (Box 60)
  - Joetta Winfield v WUI (87 Civ. 5901), 1987 (Box 60)
  - Earl Lucas and Trudy Seraneau v. WUI et al (88 Civ. 0862), 1988 (Box 60)
  - Arthur Steier v WUI (81 Civ. 4677 and 81-7848), 1981 (Box 60)
  - Earl Lucas v. Western Union International, 1982 (Box 60)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1970s-1990s (Box 61)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1978-1987 (Box 62)
  - Kozera vs IBEW, 1995 (Box 62)
  - Kozera et al v. Westchester-Fairfield Chapter, et al. 89-9072, 1989 (Box 62)
  - Max Sands v. Louis Caputo, 1967 (Box 62)
  - Sheldon v. O'Callaha, 1970 (Box 62)
  - Alfarone vs. Bernie Wolff, 1986 (Box 62)
  - Kozera v. Westchester Fairfield Chapter of National Electrical Contractors Association, Inc. (87 Civ. 5540), 1988 (Box 63)
  - Trustees of the Tapers Union Annuity and Pension Funds v. Nastasi-White, Inc et al. (91 Civ. 0650), 1981-1996 (Box 64)
  - Legal documents and decisions in John Alfarone as Trustee, et al v. Albee Drywall Partitions, Inc. (81 Civ. 1056) Predecessor Case, 1981 (Box 64)
  - Rodonich v. Local 95 & LIUNA, 1978-1985 (Box 64)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 & LIUNA, 1981 (Box 65)
  - Foreword and Introduction to "The Impact: Organized Crime Today.", April 1986 (Box 65)
  - Draft complaint of US v. LIUNA et al, undated (Box 65)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1981-1983 (Box 66)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 67)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1970s-1980s (Box 68)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 69)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 70)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 71)
  - Settlement in NLRB case: Chotowicky and Diduck vs. Local 95, charge number 2-CB-9548 (Union Hiring Hall System), undated (Box 71)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 72)
  - Transcript of Criminal Trial in US v Joseph Sherman, McNair & Roshetski (84 Cr. 205), undated (Box 72)
  - Drywall Tapers v. Local 530 (CV-81-337), 1985, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Trustees of the Tapers Insurance, Annuity and Pension Funds v. Nastasi White, Bernie Wolff Construction et al., 1990s (Box 73)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1977-1980 (Box 74)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1981-1982 (Box 75)
  - Trustees of the Tapers Insurance, Annuity and Pension Funds v. Nastasi White, Bernie Wolff Construction et al., 1980s-1990s (Box 76)
  - Unlabelled photographs [moved from box 44], undated (Box 77)
  - Cassette tape: "trail @ NABET" [moved from box 41], 1983 (Box 77)